{
  "title": "Tintin!",
  "listOfQuestions": [
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Tintin's dog?",
      "correctAnswer": "Snowy",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Bobby", "Rex", "Max"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Tintin's best human friend?",
      "correctAnswer": "Captain Haddock",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Professor Calculus", "Thomson", "Snowy"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which country does Tintin go to, to rescue Chang?",
      "correctAnswer": "Tibet",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Burma", "China", "India"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Captain Haddock's favorite curse word?",
      "correctAnswer": "Blistering barnacles",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Soggy spaghetti", "Thundering typhoons", "Curses!"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which character is a notorious villain and an antagonist to Tintin?",
      "correctAnswer": "Roberto Rastapopoulos",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Snowy", "Nestor", "General Alcazar"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of animal is Snowy?",
      "correctAnswer": "Dog",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Cat", "Fox", "Wolf"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the eccentric scientist that accompanies Tintin on some adventures?",
      "correctAnswer": "Professor Calculus",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Professor Oak", "Professor Cuthbert", "Professor Balthazar"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "In which volume does Tintin first meet Captain Haddock?",
      "correctAnswer": "The Crab with the Golden Claws",
      "wrongAnswers": ["The Secret of the Unicorn", "The Shooting Star", "The Red Sea Sharks"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the bumbling detectives that often appear in the Tintin series?",
      "correctAnswer": "Thomson and Thompson",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Moe and Larry", "Sherlock and Watson", "Houdini and Fogg"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which adventure features a mystical crystal?",
      "correctAnswer": "The Seven Crystal Balls",
      "wrongAnswers": ["The Broken Ear", "The Mystery of the Missing Memo", "The Secret of the Unicorn"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the villain in 'The Secret of the Unicorn'?",
      "correctAnswer": "Ivan Sakharine",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Rascar Capac", "Bobby Smiles", "General Alcazar"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What famous treasure is sought in 'The Secret of the Unicorn'?",
      "correctAnswer": "The treasure of the ship 'Unicorn'",
      "wrongAnswers": ["The golden lion", "The ruby of the sigil", "The crown of the king"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "In which comic does Tintin travel to the moon?",
      "correctAnswer": "Explorers on the Moon",
      "wrongAnswers": ["The Calculus Affair", "Destination Moon", "The Shooting Star"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of bird accompanies Tintin in 'The Adventures of Tintin'?",
      "correctAnswer": "None",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Parrot", "Canary", "Owl"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What color is Tintin's hair?",
      "correctAnswer": "Blonde",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Ginger", "Brown", "Black"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Tintin's home?",
      "correctAnswer": "Brussels",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Paris", "London", "Berlin"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What format does Tintin's creator, Herg√©, use for his art?",
      "correctAnswer": "Clear line style",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Cubism", "Impressionism", "Surrealism"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following books features Tintin's adventure in a desert?",
      "correctAnswer": "The Red Sea Sharks",
      "wrongAnswers": ["The Crooked Man", "Tintin in America", "The Black Island"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of pet does Captain Haddock have?",
      "correctAnswer": "None",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Cat", "Parrot", "Dog"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What historical event does Tintin encounter in 'Tintin in the Land of the Soviets'?",
      "correctAnswer": "Russian Revolution",
      "wrongAnswers": ["World War I", "French Revolution", "Spanish Civil War"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "In which comic do we first meet Professor Calculus?",
      "correctAnswer": "The Secret of the Unicorn",
      "wrongAnswers": ["The Seven Crystal Balls", "TinTin in America", "Tintin in Tibet"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What inspires Tintin's adventures?",
      "correctAnswer": "Investigative journalism",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Real estate", "Scientific research", "Art"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "In the series, who often helps Tintin in investigations?",
      "correctAnswer": "Captain Haddock",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Rascar Capac", "General Alcazar", "Dupont and Dupond"],
      "timeout": 10
    }
  ],
  "time given": ""
}

